

KRBRRA 119, KRB Road

- Thiruvankulam, Kerala, India 682305
 - +91 8593041180 •
 - jeevansaju1@gmail.com •
 - linkedIn: jeevan-saju-66834a194•

OBJECTIVE ·····

Resourceful Server/System Administrator consistently responds to wide range of technical challenges with focused and creative approach. Highly effective at problem solving and decision making. 1 year of progressive experience in Server Management as well as providing the IT support needed for my firm. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FHC INDIA PVT LTD, ERNAKULAM, INDIA

SERVER ADMINISTRATOR, October 2021 - Present

- Maintained applications to keep software current with necessary software updates and upgrades.
- Backed up company data to distributed storage centers to avoid massive data loss.
- Configured networks for smooth, reliable operation to meet business processes and objectives.
- Identified and immediately resolved all issues of the client systems.
- Performed day-to-day LAN and WAN administration, maintenance and support.
- Monitored system performance and responded to alerts.
- Managed computer operation scheduling, backup, storage and retrieval functions.
- Identified and immediately resolved issues with network devices.
- Providing feedbacks to software developers regarding any bugs or issues.

THOMASMOUNT PVT CONSULTING ERNAKULAM, INDIA

EXECUTIVE RESOURCING, March 2021 - October 2021

- External Recruitment & Internal Recruitment
- This involves tasks such as putting together job ads, sourcing candidates, reviewing their qualifications, negotiating the salary and everything else involved in hiring new staff.

EDUCATION

A P J ABDUL KALAM UNIVERSITY COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING, KOTTARAKKARA, KERALA

Bachelor of Technology, July 2015- March 2019 Computer Science Engineering

HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION St. IGNATIUS HSS HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION

HSE, May 2013 - May 2015 Computer Science

TECHNICAL PROFILE

- Linux
- Windows
- Cloud Storage
- Trouble shooting
- LAN
- SQL
- HTML
- CSS
- Microsoft Office
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel

CERTIFICATE

KELTRON Internship

- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS

PERSONAL INFORMATIONS

Date Of Birth: 28/10/1996
Father's Name: Saju PJ
Nationality: INDIAN
Marital Status: Single

LANGUAGES

- English
- Malayalam

SKILLS

- Flexibility of Attitude
- Great Communication
- Situation Handling
- Organizing Skill
- Adaptability
- Self Motivated

I hereby declare that the above particulars of facts and information stated are correct to the best of my belief and knowledge.